aacc.edu 2014-11-11

# Technology Services - Your Privacy and Our Web Site

**Anne Arundel Community College Privacy Statement**

Thank you for visiting the Anne Arundel Community College website. Information security and individual privacy are a priority at Anne Arundel Community College. The College strives to protect the information that it collects and uses, and any information collected is used for College business purposes only. The following further details information handling practices used by Anne Arundel Community College to protect information and promote privacy.

 **Personally Identifiable Information and Privacy**

Personally Identifiable Information including financial information that may be provided during college processes (admissions, registration,  purchasing, employment, etc.) is used solely for those purposes and is restricted and protected in accordance with College policy and procedure, relevant State and Federal laws and regulations, and by utilizing secure network and data storage technologies. Anne Arundel Community College does not sell or share non-public personally identifiable information or client lists with any third party, unless required to complete a transaction in the ordinary course of business, or by State or Federal law or regulation such as the Maryland Public Information Act (PIA) or the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA).

 **Information Automatically Logged by the Use of College Web sites**

Official Anne Arundel Community College web sites. These servers collect and log information according to industry standards in order to analyze usage of the web site and to improve its design and usability. The information that is logged does not contain personal data about the user and is used only internally by the college. 

 **Cookies**

AACC uses cookies which are small text files that can store information to your browser as a result of a website visit. They do not collect any personal identifiable information (PII) but instead track traffic trends, usage patterns, customer behavior and other data we use to improve the user experience.  

 **Direct Marketing**

AACC uses tracking pixels (also known as web beacons, transparent GIFs, clear GIFs, pixel GIFs, or pixel tags) which are tiny invisible images that allow the college to track activities based on pages you visit. Tracking pixels redeliver advertising that displays on other sites based on previous interaction with AACC’s website. This marketing effort does not collect any PII. If you wish to opt-out of this web tracking provided by Recrue Media, please do so by visiting <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers> or you can alternatively disable cookies on your browser.  

 **Links to Other Sites**

Anne Arundel Community College provides links to other web sites. When you leave an official Anne Arundel Community College web site please be aware that Anne Arundel Community College is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites.

 **Privacy Statement Updates**

Periodically, this privacy statement may be updated to accommodate changes to our information security program or web environment.

 **Questions**

If you have questions about the content, please contact [webmaster@aacc.edu.](mailto:webmaster@aacc.edu "Email the webmaster")
